<Advertisement>  
  <Ad active="true">
	<Content>
		<![CDATA[
		<div id="ADCONTENT">
<table class="contentinner" cellpadding="5" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
<tr>
<td align="center" valign="top">
<a href="http://store.taylorprotocols.com/The-Core-Values-Handbook-P46.aspx"><img src="images/cvhcf300.jpg" border="0" width="189" height="300" ></a>
</td>
<td>
    <div class="content">
        <p><strong><b>The Core Values Handbook</b></strong></p> 
	<br/>
	<p><b>“Employment Pre-Selection Science&trade; from Taylor Protocols is the most powerful business optimization system I have ever found!”</b><br/>
	Chuck Orton, President<br/>
	M&M Comfort Systems</p>
	<br/>
	<p>The Core Values Index&trade; (CVI&trade;) characterizes and measures each person’s Real Core Values Nature&trade;.  This is the essential self that Abraham Maslow asserted is the innate unchanging nature in each of us that causes us to want to make our unique contribution.  It is that part of us that determines where we fit, where we can each make our highest and best contribution.  Fully automated Employment Pre-Selection&trade;, team building, conflict resolution, leadership training, management, restructuring departments, and businesses- all business and personal decisions are improved for those who have the advantage of the Core Values Index&trade; and the powerful Taylor Protocols&trade; that effectively put this revolutionary technology to work.</p>
	<br/>
	<p>Inside you will find:
	<ul>
	<li>A complete handbook on the Core Values Index&trade;, its interpretation and its direct personal and business applications.</li>
	<li>An introduction to the amazing Taylor Protocols that utilize the CVI&trade; for the optimization of any kind of business.  This assessment and the Taylor Protocols were developed in the fires of 400 business turn-around and business restructuring projects.</li>
	<li>A first look at the revolutionary Employment Pre-Selection Science&trade; that David Mashburn, Ph.D., asserts “…is the first system to characterize and quantify the innate unchanging nature of individuals, and the first employment system to connect this unchanging nature with the tasks of the job.”</li>
	</ul>
	</p>

        <table cellpadding="4" cellspacing="0">
		<tr>
		<th align="right">
		Author:</th>
		<td>
		Lynn Ellsworth Taylor</td>
		</tr>
		<tr>
		<th align="right">
		ISBN:</th>
		<td>
		978-0-615-16622-3</td>
		</tr>
		</table>

	</div>
</td>
</tr>
</table>

</div>

		]]>
	</Content>      
   </Ad>
</Advertisement>